Guide to the Wolfgang F. Stolper Papers, 1892-2001 (bulk [1930s-1990s]
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 2002-0207 (Box 14)
  - Contents of Box 1: (Box 1)
    - 1941-1999 (Box 1)
      - Correspondence (Box 1)
      - Professional Writings (Box 1)
      - Lectures (Box 1)
      - Nigerian Material (Box 1)
  - Contents of Box 2: (Box 2)
    - 1928-1996 (Box 2)
      - Correspondence (Box 2)
      - Professional Writings (Box 2)
  - Contents of Box 3: (Box 3)
    - 1930-1998 ( bulk 1980s-1990s) (Box 3)
      - Correspondence (Box 3)
  - Contents of Box 4: (Box 4)
    - 1981-1998 (Box 4)
      - Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Contents of Box 5: (Box 5)
    - 1968-1998 (Box 5)
      - Correspondence (Box 5)
  - Contents of Box 6: (Box 6)
    - 1960-1987 ( bulk 1960-1964) (Box 6)
      - Correspondence (Box 6)
      - Professional Writings (Box 6)
      - Nigerian Material (Box 6)
      - Diaries, 1961 and 1962 (Box 6)
  - Contents of Box 7: (Box 7)
    - 1960-1998 (Box 7)
      - Correspondence (Box 7)
      - Professional Writings (Box 7)
      - Diaries (Box 7)
  - Contents of Box 8: (Box 8)
    - 1960-1994 (Box 8)
      - Correspondence (Box 8)
      - Professional Writings (Box 8)
      - Nigerian Material (Box 8)
      - Diaries (Box 8)
  - Contents of Box 9: (Box 9)
    - 1944-1989 (Box 9)
      - Professional Writings (Box 9)
  - Contents of Box 10: (Box 10)
    - 1958-1992 (Box 10)
      - Professional Writings (Box 10)
      - Liberian Material (Box 10)
  - Contents of Box 11: (Box 11)
    - 1959-1995 (Box 11)
      - Correspondence (Box 11)
      - Professional Writings (Box 11)
      - Diaries (Box 11)
      - Handwritten Notes (Box 11)
      - Nigerian Material (Box 11)
  - Contents of Box 12: (Box 12)
    - 1955-1997 (Box 12)
      - Correspondence (Box 12)
      - Professional Writings (Box 12)
      - Diaries (Box 12)
        These diaries correspond to Stolper's time in Nigeria
      - Lecture Notes (Box 12)
      - Printed Material (Box 12)
  - Contents of Box 13: (Box 13)
    - 1960-1995 (Box 13)
      - Correspondence (Box 13)
      - Professional Writings (Box 13)
      - Diaries (Box 13)
        Included are three diaries th at correspond to Stolper's time in Nigeria
  - Contents of Box 14: (Box 14)
    - 1928-1988 (Box 14)
      - Correspondence (Box 14)
      - Professional Writings (Box 14)
      - Diaries (Box 14)
      - Travel Material (Box 14)
      - Shumpeter Letters (Box 14)
  - Contents of Box 15: (Box 15)
    - 1940-1996 (Box 15)
      - Correspondence (Box 15)
      - Professional Writings (Box 15)
  - Contents of Box 16: (Box 16)
    - 1973-2001 (Box 16)
      - Correspondence (Box 16)
      - Professional Writings (Box 16)
      - Handwritten Notes (Box 16)
  - Contents of Box 17: (Box 17)
    - 1959-2001 (Box 17)
      - Correspondence (Box 17)
      - Professional Writings (Box 17)
      - Diaries (Box 17)
      - Federation of Nigeria National Development Plan 1962-1968 (Box 17)
  - Contents of Box 18: (Box 18)
    - 1919-1990 (Box 18)
      - Correspondence (Box 18)
      - Printed Material (Box 18)
        Includes some Printed Material related to Nigeria
  - Contents of Box 19: (Box 19)
    - 1892-1999 (Box 19)
      - Correspondence (Box 19)
      - Handwritten Notes (Box 19)
      - Scumpeter Society Information (Box 19)
  - Contents of Box 20: (Box 20)
    - 1945-1987 (Box 20)
      - Correspondence (Box 20)
      - Nigerian Material (Box 20)
  - Contents of Box 21: (Box 21)
    - 1947-1987 (Box 21)
      - Correspondence (Box 21)
      - Diaries (Box 21)
      - Doctoral Committee and Thesis Comments (Box 21)
  - Contents of Box 22: (Box 22)
    - 1931-1985 (Box 22)
      - Correspondence (Box 22)
      - Professional Writings (Box 22)
      - Handwritten notes (Box 22)
      - Teaching Materials (Box 22)
        Includes test copies, lectures and syllabi
  - Contents of Box 23 (Box 23)
    - 1936-1988 (Box 23)
      - Correspondence (Box 23)
  - Contents of Box 24: (Box 24)
    - 1953-1972 (Box 24)
      - Correspondence (Box 24)
      - Travel Material (Box 24)